<cfprocessingdirective suppresswhitespace="yes" pageencoding="ISO-8859-1">

<cfsilent>

<!--

L10N Resource File

Section: Monitoring

Locale: English (en)

Find the requested resource by id

-->

</cfsilent>

<cfswitch expression="#ATTRIBUTES.id#">

<cfcase value="ms_pagename">Monitoring Settings</cfcase>

<cfcase value="monitoringsettings_header">Server Monitoring &gt; Settings</cfcase>

<cfcase value="ms_monitor_enable">Enable Monitoring</cfcase>

<cfcase value="ms_monitor_enable_tip">
When checked, indicates that monitoring is enabled. 
If unchecked, it will disable monitoring.
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="ms_profiling_enable">Enable Profiling</cfcase>

<cfcase value="ms_profiling_enable_tip">
When checked, indicates that profiling is enabled. 
If unchecked, it will disable profiling.
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="memorytracking_enable">Enable Memory Tracking</cfcase>

<cfcase value="memorytracking_enable_tip">
When checked, indicates that memory tracking is enabled. 
If unchecked, it will disable memory tracking.
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="monitoringserversettings_header">Monitoring Server Settings</cfcase>

<cfcase value="ms_monitoringserver_enable">Enable Monitoring Server</cfcase>

<cfcase value="ms_monitoringserver_enable_tip">
When checked, indicates that separate monitoring server is enabled. 
If unchecked, it will disable separate monitoring server.
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="monitoringServerPort">Monitoring Server Port</cfcase>

<cfcase value="error_portinuse">Port already in use. Please provide a different port.</cfcase>

<cfcase value="error_settings">There was an error while settings up server. Please check logs for more details.</cfcase>

<cfcase value="monitoringserverPort_tip">
Specify the port on which monitoring server should start. This server will handle monitoring requests. 
Make sure that Monitoring Server is enabled and the port is not blocked.
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="ms_error_portvalidation">
Port Value must be numeric and greater than 0.
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="ms_error_tmpupd"><cfoutput>
Unable to update template handler information.
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#<br />
</cfoutput></cfcase>

<cfcase value="invalidSnapshotFile">Invalid snapshot file or snapshot file does not exist :</cfcase>

<cfcase value="flash_remoting_disabled">
Flash remoting should be enabled to run either of Server Monitor or Multiserver Monitor.
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="pageHeader_clientvars1">Server Monitoring &gt; Server Monitor</cfcase>

<cfcase value="servermonitor">
The Server Monitor is an Adobe Flash application that provides information about ColdFusion server operation. To use the Server Monitor, you must have Adobe Flash Player 9 installed.<br>
<br>
Use the buttons at the top of the Server Monitor to do the following:
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
<tr><td>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Start Monitoring - Turns on all monitoring.</td></tr>
<tr><td>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Start Profiling - Turns on monitoring of all tags, functions, and query execution times.</td></tr>
<tr><td>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Start Memory Tracking - Turns on tracking of memory by different scopes. If Profiling is also on, tracks memory used by individual tags, functions, and queries.</td></tr>
</table>
<br>
Memory usage information displayed in the Server Monitor is estimated and may vary from actual memory usage. Use the information as an indicator rather than an absolute measure.<br>
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="launch_sm">
Click the button on the right to launch the Server Monitor ...
  </cfcase>

<cfcase value="launch_server_monitor">Launch Server Monitor</cfcase>

<cfcase value="pageHeader_clientvars2">Server Monitoring &gt; Multiserver Monitor</cfcase>

<cfcase value="remotemonitor">
The Multiserver Monitor is an Adobe Flash application that you can use to remotely monitor multiple ColdFusion instances. To use the Multiserver Monitor, you must have Adobe Flash Player 9 installed.<br>
<br>
Use the tabs at the top of the Multiserver Monitor to do the following:
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
<tr><td>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Quick View - Displays the status of all registered servers in a icon view format.</td></tr>
<tr><td>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Detailed View - Displays the status of all registered servers in a tabular format.</td></tr>
<tr><td>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Add Server - Displays the registration panel for adding new servers.</td></tr>
<tr><td>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Errors - Displays the last connection error for each registered server.</td></tr>
</table>
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="launch_msm">
Click the button on the right to launch the Multiserver Monitor ...
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="launch_multiserver_monitor">Launch Multiserver Monitor</cfcase>

<cfcase value="pageHeader_clientvars3">Server Manager</cfcase>

<cfcase value="servermanager">
The Server Manager is an AIR application which allows management of multiple servers
<br>
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="launch_smanager">
Click the button on the right to launch the ColdFusion Server Manager ...
</cfcase>

<cfcase value="launch_server_manager">Launch Server Manager</cfcase>

<cfcase value="alternatecontent_cf">
                  This content requires the Adobe Flash Player. <a href=http://www.adobe.com/go/getflash/>Get Flash
                </cfcase>


<cfdefaultcase><cfset bSuccess="false"/></cfdefaultcase>

</cfswitch>

</cfprocessingdirective>


