<cfprocessingdirective suppresswhitespace="yes" pageencoding="ISO-8859-1">
<cfsilent>
<!--
L10N Resource File
Section: Settings
Locale: English (en)
Find the requested resource by id
-->
</cfsilent>
<cfswitch expression="#ATTRIBUTES.id#">

<cfcase value="statmess">Server has been updated successfully</cfcase>
<cfcase value="click_normal">Click the button on the right to update</cfcase>
<cfcase value="alert">ALERT!</cfcase>
<cfcase value="important_notice">Important notice about last submission</cfcase>
<cfcase value="click_return">Click arrow on left to return without submitting changes</cfcase>
<cfcase value="submit_changes">Submit Changes</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_clear_cache_submit">Template Cache Cleared.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_pagename">Caching</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pageHeader_caching">
Server Settings &gt; Caching</cfcase>
<cfcase value="template_cache_size">Maximum number of cached templates</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_template_cacheSize_desc">
Limits the number of templates cached using template caching. If the cache is set to a small value, ColdFusion might re-process your templates. If your server has a sufficient amount of memory, you can achieve optimum performance by setting this value to the total number of all of your ColdFusion templates. Setting the cache to a high value does not automatically reduce available memory because ColdFusion caches templates incrementally.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_trusted_cache">Trusted cache</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_trusted_cache_desc">
When checked, any requested files found to currently reside in the template cache will not be inspected for potential updates. For sites where
templates are not updated during the life of the server, this minimizes
file system overhead. This setting does not require restarting the server.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="in_request_template_cache">Cache Template In Request</cfcase>
<cfcase value="in_request_template_cache_text">
   When checked, any requested files will be inspected only once for potential updates within a request. If unchecked,
   requested file will be inspected for changes each and everytime when its accessed within the same request. For application where
   templates/components are not expected to reflect updates within the same request, this minimizes file system overhead. This setting does not require restarting the server.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_component_cache">Component cache</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_component_cache_desc">
When checked, component path resolution is cached and not resolved again. This setting does not require restarting the server.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="save_class_files">Save class files</cfcase>
<cfcase value="save_class_files_desc">
When you select this option, the class files generated by ColdFusion are saved to disk for reuse after the server restarts.
Adobe recommends this for production systems.  During development, Adobe recommends that you do not select this option.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cacheRealPath">Cache web server paths</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cacheRealPath_desc">
Caches page paths on single-site web server installations, which provides improved performance.
You must restart the server for this change to take effect.
<br /><br />
Note: Do not select this option when you use ColdFusion with multiple website systems.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_Max_cachedQueries">Maximum number of cached queries</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_Max_cachedQueries_desc">
Limits the maximum number of cached queries that the server will maintain.
Cached queries allow for retrieval of result sets from memory rather
than through a database transaction. Since the queries reside in memory,
and query result set sizes differ, there must be some user-imposed limit
to the number of queries that are cached. When this value is exceeded,
the oldest query is dropped from the cache and is replaced with the
specified query.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_clear_cache_button">Clear Template Cache Now</cfcase>
<cfcase value="caching_clear_cache_desc">Click the button below to clear the template cache. ColdFusion will re-load templates into memory the next time they are requested and recompile them if they have been modified.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="component_caching_clear_cache_button">Clear Component Cache Now</cfcase>
<cfcase value="component_caching_clear_cache_desc">Click the button below to clear the component cache. ColdFusion will ignore the resolved path for components and try the resolution again.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="provide_cache_path">You must specify a cache path.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxEngineRange">Please enter in an integer number between 1 and 5 for number of charting threads.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="max_cache_size">Please enter in a number between 1 and 1500 for number of cached images.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="charting_pagename">Charting Settings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pageHeader_charting">
Server Settings &gt;  Charting</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_graphmem">Memory Cache</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_graphdisk">Disk Cache</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_graphct">Cache type</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_graphcache">Charts can be cached either in memory or to disk.  In memory caching is faster, but more memory intensive.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_graphmax">Maximum number of cached images</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_graphmaxtext">
Specifies the maximum number of charts to store in the cache.  When the cache is full and a new chart is generated, the oldest chart in the cache is discarded. Caching charts results in multiple requests for the same chart being much faster, because the chart is generated only once.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_graphthread">Maximum number of charting threads</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_graphthreadtext">Specifies the maximum number of chart requests that can be processed concurrently. The minimum number is 1; the maximum is 5. The higher the number, the more memory intensive.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_cachelocation">Disk cache location</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_browse">Browse Server</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_cachelocationtext">When caching to disk, specifies the directory in which to store the generated charts.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="registry_label">Registry</cfcase>
<cfcase value="registry_desc">System registry.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cookie_label">Cookie</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cookie_desc">Client based text file.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="x_badpdata">
Purge Interval must be numeric and greater then or equal to zero.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="client_tooquick">
Purge Interval should not be less than every 30 minutes.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_edit_pagename"><cfoutput>Add/Edit Client Store: #CALLER.thisStore#</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_pagename">Client Variables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_desc">Description</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_create_tables_manual_instructions.">
Your data source requires you to manually create the necessary database tables to store your client variables. See the Online Help for details.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_create_tables">Create Client database tables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_create_tables_tip">
Enable this option only if this is the first time you are configuring
the current data source for client variable storage. If the current data source has
already been configured for client variable storage, do not enable this option.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_purge">Purge data for clients that remain unvisited for</cfcase>
<cfcase value="days">days</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_purge_tip">
Enable this option if you want ColdFusion to periodically purge client data 
that has not been accessed in the specified number of days. 
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_edit_cluster_warn">
If this data source is being used by more than one ColdFusion server, as in the case of clustered servers, make sure that only one server in the cluster is configured to purge client data.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_disable_globals">Disable global client variable updates</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cf_updates_globals_tip">
This option controls how ColdFusion updates global client variables, such as HITCOUNT and LASTVISIT. If updates
are disabled, ColdFusion updates these variables only when they are set or modified. If updates are enabled, 
ColdFusion updates global client variables for each page request.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pageHeader_clientvars">
Server Settings &gt; Client Variables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="configure_datasources">
Client variables let you store user information and preferences between sessions.
The Administrator setting is only used when no ClientStorage attribute is specified in a cfapplication tag. 
To add a ColdFusion data source to the list of available client storage mechanisms, select 
the data source from the drop-down list, and click the Add button. 
To set the data source as the default storage mechanism, select the radio button and Click Apply.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="selectDS">Select Data Source to Add as Client Store</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_add">Add</cfcase>
<cfcase value="activateCS">Select Default Storage Mechanism for Client Sessions</cfcase>
<cfcase value="actions">Actions</cfcase>
<cfcase value="storage_name">Storage Name</cfcase>
<cfcase value="description">Description</cfcase>
<cfcase value="delete_client_confirmation">Are you sure you want to delete this Client Variable Store?</cfcase>
<cfcase value="edit">Edit</cfcase>
<cfcase value="delete">Delete</cfcase>
<cfcase value="none">None</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_apply">Apply</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_purgeinterval">Purge Interval</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cf_purge_globals_tip">
This option controls how often ColdFusion executes a purge operation on your client stores. 
If your client stores are configured to be purged, this will be rate at which the operation will be executed. 
It defaults to 1 hour 7 minutes and should not be less than every 30 minutes.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="hours">hours</cfcase>
<cfcase value="minutes">minutes</cfcase>
<cfcase value="no_stores">No client stores defined.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="font_pagename">Font Management</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pageHeader_fontmanagement">
Server Settings &gt; Font Management</cfcase>
<cfcase value="font_register">Register New Font(s) with ColdFusion</cfcase>
<cfcase value="font_newpath">New Font/Font Directory</cfcase>
<cfcase value="delete_font_confirmation">
Are you sure you want to delete this font?
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_add_font">Add</cfcase>
<cfcase value="font_registerUserDefined">User Defined Fonts</cfcase>
<cfcase value="user_actions">Actions</cfcase>
<cfcase value="user_fontfamily">Font Family</cfcase>
<cfcase value="user_fontface">Font Face</cfcase>
<cfcase value="user_fontpsname">Postscript Name</cfcase>
<cfcase value="user_fonttype">Font Type</cfcase>
<cfcase value="user_fontuseablein">Useable In</cfcase>
<cfcase value="user_path">Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="fontpaths">Current System Fonts</cfcase>
<cfcase value="system_fontfamily">Font Family</cfcase>
<cfcase value="system_fontface">Font Face</cfcase>
<cfcase value="system_fontpsname">Postscript Name</cfcase>
<cfcase value="system_fonttype">Font Type</cfcase>
<cfcase value="system_fontpath">Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="font_nopathsfound">No fonts found.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="vm_pagename">Java and JVM Settings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="java_jvm_pageHeader">
Server Settings &gt; Java and JVM</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jvm_header">
Java and JVM settings control the way ColdFusion starts the Java Virtual Machine when it starts.  You can control settings like what classpaths are used and how memory is allocated as well as add custom command line arguments.  Changing these settings requires restarting ColdFusion.  If you enter an incorrect setting, ColdFusion may not restart properly.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jvm_backups">
Backups of the jvm.config file are created when you hit the submit button. You can use this backup
to restore from a critical change.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jvm_virtual_path">Java Virtual Machine Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="specify_location_jvm">Specifies the location of the Java Virtual Machine.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="megabyte">MB</cfcase>
<cfcase value="initial_memory_size">Minimum JVM Heap Size</cfcase>
<cfcase value="max_memory_size">Maximum JVM Heap Size</cfcase>
<cfcase value="max_min_mem_desc">
The Memory Size settings determine the amount of memory that the JVM can use for programs and data.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cf_class_path">ColdFusion Class Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="specify_class_paths_jvm">Specifies any additional class paths for the JVM, with multiple directories separated by  commas.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jvm_args">JVM Arguments</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jvm_args_desc">Specifies any specific JVM initialization options, separated by spaces.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="hf_apply">For these changes to take effect, you must restart the ColdFusion Service.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="not_valid_license">The license entered was not valid.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="license_pagename">Licensing Settings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enter_license">Enter a license number.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="license_intro">
Use the form below to enter a new serial number. Depending on the serial
number you enter, various features will be turned on or turned off.
Your current edition is:
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="new_license">New License</cfcase>
<cfcase value="err_queue_timeout">Queue timeout must be a postive number</cfcase>
<cfcase value="msg_simul_req">Simultaneous Request</cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_pagename">Request Tuning</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pageHeader_requesttuning">
Server Settings &gt; Request Tuning</cfcase>
<cfcase value="request_limit">Request Limits</cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_max_req">Maximum number of simultaneous Template requests</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_max_req_tip">
Restricts the number of simultaneously processed requests. Use this setting to increase overall
system performance for heavy load applications. Requests beyond the specified limit are queued.
On Standard Edition, you must restart ColdFusion to enable this setting.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_max_req_tip">
The number of CFML page requests that can be processed concurrently. Use this setting to increase overall
system performance for heavy load applications. Requests beyond the specified limit are queued.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_max_flash">Maximum number of simultaneous Flash Remoting requests</cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_max_flash_tip">
The number of Flash Remoting requests that can be processed concurrently.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_max_webservice">Maximum number of simultaneous Web Service requests</cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_max_webservice_tip">
The number of Web Service requests that can be processed concurrently.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_max_cfc">Maximum number of simultaneous CFC function requests</cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_max_cfc_tip">
The number of ColdFusion Component methods that can be processed concurrently via HTTP.
This does not affect invocation of CFC methods from within CFML, only methods requested via
an HTTP request.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jrun_limit">JRun Master Request Limits (restart required)</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxJrunThread">Maximum number of running JRun threads</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxActiveJRun_tip"><cfoutput>
Maximum number of JRun handler threads that will run concurrently.
This is the number of request threads that the underlying JRun J2EE application server
will run at the same time.  This includes any non-ColdFusion requests such as JSP pages.
Generally this value should be greater than the sum (currently #CALLER.limitsum#) of the request limits above .
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxQueuedJRun">Maximum number of queued JRun Threads</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxQueuedJRun_tip">
Maximum number of requests that JRun can accept at any one time.
This is the number of requests that the underlying JRun J2EE application server accepts at the same time.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="tag_limit">Tag Limit Settings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxReports">Maximum number of simultaneous Report threads</cfcase>
<cfcase value="reportThread_tip">
The maximum number of ColdFusion reports that can be processed concurrently.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxCFThread">Maximum number of threads available for CFTHREAD</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxCFThread_tip">
    The maximum number of threads created by CFTHREAD that will be run concurrently.
Threads created by CFTHREAD in excess of this are queued.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxCFThread_tip_standard">
On Standard Edition, the maximum limit is 10.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="queue_limit">Queue Timeout Settings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="queueTimeout">Timeout requests waiting in queue after</cfcase>
<cfcase value="seconds">seconds</cfcase>
<cfcase value="queueTimeout_tip"><cfoutput>
If a request has waited in the queue for this long, timeout the request.
This value should be at least as long as the Request Timeout
setting (currently #REQUEST.runtime.requestSettings.timeoutRequestTimeLimit# seconds).
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="queue_timeout_page">Request Queue Timeout Page</cfcase>
<cfcase value="queuetimeout_tip_1">
Specify a relative path from the web root to an HTML page to send to clients when a template request times out before running,
for example /CFIDE/timeout.html. The page you specify cannot contain CFML.
If you do not specify a page, clients receive a 500 Request Timeout error when their request does not run.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_no_name">Please enter a valid name for the mapping</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_invalid_path">Please enter a valid path for the mapping</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_duplicate_logical_path">The logical path entered already exists</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_pagename">ColdFusion Mappings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pageHeader_mappings">
Server Settings &gt;  Mappings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_welcome">
ColdFusion mappings let the cfinclude and cfmodule tags access pages that are outside the Web root. 
If you specify a path that starts with the mapping's logical path in these tags, ColdFusion looks 
for the page using the mapping's directory path.
<br /><br />

ColdFusion also uses mappings to find ColdFusion components (CFCs). The cfinvoke and cfobject tags and 
CreateObject function look for CFCs in the mapped directories.
<br /><br />

<b>Note:</b> These mappings are independent of web server virtual directories.  
If you would like to create a virtual directory to access a given directory through a URL, 
please consult your web server documentation. 
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="add_edit_mapping">Add / Edit ColdFusion Mappings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_logical_path">Logical Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_dir_path">Directory Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_map_update">Update Mapping</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_map_delete">Delete Mapping</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_map_reset">Reset</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_add_map">Add Mapping</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_active">Active ColdFusion Mappings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="sort_lpath">Sort by Logical Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="sort_dpath">Sort by Drive Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="delete_mapping_confirmation">Are you sure you want to delete this ColdFusion Mapping?</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_nomappings">No mappings are active.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="numeric_value">All timeout values must be numeric and greater than or equal to 0.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_pagename">Memory Variables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pageHeader_memoryvars">
Server Settings &gt;  Memory Variables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_welcome">
Application variables expire when you restart the ColdFusion server. 
Session variables expire when the user's session ends. Both types of variables also 
expire after a time-out period that you specify on this page or in the cfapplication tag. 
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_useJ2eeSession">Use J2EE session variables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_appenable">Enable Application Variables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_sessenable">Enable Session Variables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxtime">Maximum Timeout</cfcase>
<cfcase value="maxTimeoutDescription">
These values specify the maximum time-out period that you can use in a cfapplication tag.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_appvars">Application Variables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_days">days</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_hours">hours</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_mins">mins</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_secs">secs</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_sessvars">Session Variables</cfcase>
<cfcase value="defaultime">Default Timeout</cfcase>
<cfcase value="defaultTimeoutDescription">
These values specify the time-out period that ColdFusion uses if you do not specify an application-specific value in the cfapplication tag.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="localofficeupdated">
Local OpenOffice configuration updated.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="remotesofficeupdated">
Remote OpenOffice configuration updated.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="remotesofficedelete">
Remote OpenOffice configuration removed.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="document_pagename">OpenOffice Configuration</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pageHeader_documentmanagement">
Server Settings &gt; Document</cfcase>
<cfcase value="openoffice_register_local">Configure local OpenOffice with ColdFusion</cfcase>
<cfcase value="officePath">OpenOffice Directory</cfcase>
<cfcase value="browser_server">Browse Server</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_add_office">Add</cfcase>
<cfcase value="openoffice_register_remote">Configure remote OpenOffice with ColdFusion</cfcase>
<cfcase value="remoteHost">Remote Host</cfcase>
<cfcase value="remotePort">Remote Port</cfcase>
<cfcase value="button_delete_office">Delete</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cant_find_template_handler">
The file specified as the site wide missing template handler does not exist.
The default missing template handler will be used until a replacement is created.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="empty_securejsonprefix">
The JSON prefix cannot be an empty string.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_pagename">Server Settings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pageHeader_serversettings">
Server Settings &gt; Settings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_timeout">Timeout Requests after</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_timeout_tip">
When checked, requests that take longer than the specified time are terminated.
This prevents unusually long requests from occupying server resources and
impairing the performance of other requests.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="perapp_enable_per_app_settings">Enable Per App Settings</cfcase>
<cfcase value="perapp_enable_per_app_settings_desc">
When checked, per application settings are enabled server-wide.
If unchecked, per app settings are disabled server-wide.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ws_enable">Use UUID for cftoken</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ws_welcome">
Configures ColdFusion to use a UUID rather than a random number
for client and session variable cftoken values. A UUID guarantees a unique identifier for the token.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enablehttpst">Enable HTTP status codes</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enablehttpsttext">
Enables ColdFusion to set HTTP error status codes when ColdFusion errors are returned to the browser. ColdFusion
sets an error status code of 404 if the template is not found and an error status code of 500 for server errors.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enablewhite">Enable Whitespace Management</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enablewhitetext">
Reduces the file size of the pages that ColdFusion returns to the browser by removing many of the
extra spaces, tabs, and carriage returns that ColdFusion might otherwise persist from the CFML source file.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="disable_CFCTypeCheck_settings">Disable CFC Type Check</cfcase>
<cfcase value="disableCFCTypeCheck_settings_desc">
When checked, UDF arguments of CFC type is not validated. The arguments are treated as type "ANY".
Use this setting in a production environment only.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="disableServiceFactory">Disable access to internal ColdFusion Java components</cfcase>
<cfcase value="disableServiceFactoryttext">
Disables the ability for CFML code to access and create Java objects that are part of the
internal ColdFusion implementation. This prevents an unauthenticated CFML template
from reading or modifying administration and configuration information for this server.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="secureJSON">Prefix serialized JSON with</cfcase>
<cfcase value="secureJSONtext">
Protects web services which return JSON data from cross-site scripting attacks by prefixing
serialized JSON strings with a custom prefix.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enableInMemoryFileSystem">Enable In-Memory File System</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enableInMemoryFileSystemText">
Enables the In-Memory File System support
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="inMemoryFileSystemLimit">Memory Limit for In-Memory Virtual File System</cfcase>
<cfcase value="inMemoryFileSystemLimit_text">
Specify memory limit in MB for In-Memory Virtual File System.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enableWatcher">Watch configuration files for changes (check every </cfcase>
<cfcase value="enableWacherText">
Causes ColdFusion to watch its configuration files and automatically reload them if they change.
This is required if you deploy ColdFusion in a Websphere ND vertical cluster, as multiple instances of ColdFusion share the
same configuration files. Most installations should not enable this feature.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="visableMeasuresLabel">Enable Visible Measures Tracking</cfcase>
<cfcase value="visableMeasuresDesc">
(Beta only) Enables collection of performance and usage information for selected sections of ColdFusion code.
ColdFusion automatically uploads this information periodically to the Adobe website.
If your site does not allow this type of automatic upload, clear this check box.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enableGlobalScriptProtect">Enable Global Script Protection</cfcase>
<cfcase value="globalScriptProtectDesc">
Specify whether to protect Form, URL, CGI, and Cookie scope variables from cross-site scripting attacks.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="allowExtraAttributesInAttrColl">Allow Extra Attributes in AttributeCollection</cfcase>
<cfcase value="allowExtraAttributesInAttrCollDesc">
Specify whether ColdFusion tags can pass non-standard attributes in the attributecollection structure.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cFaaSGeneratedFilesExpiryTime">Clear temporary files created during CFaaS after</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cFaaSGeneratedFilesExpiryTime_tip">
Causes ColdFusion to delete temporary files created during CF as a Service(CFaaS) operation after the specified time since its creation.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="CFFORMScriptSrc">Default ScriptSrc Directory </cfcase>
<cfcase value="cfformscriptsrc_text">
Specify the default path (relative to the web root) to the directory containing the cfform.js file.<br />
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="GoogleMapKey">Google Map API Key</cfcase>
<cfcase value="googlemapkey_text">
Specify Google Map api license key.<br />
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enableServerCFC">Component with onServerStart( ) method</cfcase>
<cfcase value="enableServerCFC_text">
Specify the absolute path to a CFC having onServerStart() method, like "c:\server.cfc". Or specify a dot delimited CFC path under webroot, like "a.b.server". By default, ColdFusion will look for server.cfc under webroot.<br />
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="applicationCFCLookup">Application.cfc/Application.cfm lookup order</cfcase>
<cfcase value="defaultApplicationCFCLookup">Default order</cfcase>
<cfcase value="tillwebRootApplicationCFCLookup">Until webroot</cfcase>
<cfcase value="inWebRootApplicationCFCLookup">In webroot</cfcase>
<cfcase value="applicationCFCLookup_text">
Specify the option ColdFusion should use to search for an Application.cfc/Application.cfm if it is not found in the current folder. By default, ColdFusion
will search until the system root.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_missing_template">Missing Template Handler</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_missing_template_tip">
Specify the relative path to the template to execute when ColdFusion cannot find a requested template.<br />
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_err_handler">Site-wide Error Handler</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_err_handler_tip">
Specify the relative path to a template to execute when ColdFusion
encounters errors while processing a request.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="limitheader">Request Size Limits</cfcase>
<cfcase value="postSizeLimit">Maximum size of post data</cfcase>
<cfcase value="postSizeLimit_tip">
Limits the amount of data that can be posted to the server in a single request. ColdFusion rejects requests larger than the specified limit.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="throttleThreshold">Request Throttle Threshold</cfcase>
<cfcase value="throttleThreshold_tip">
Requests smaller than the specified limit are not handled by the throttle.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="throttleMemory">Request Throttle Memory</cfcase>
<cfcase value="throttleMemory_tip">
Limits total memory size for the throttle.
ColdFusion queues requests if there is not enough total memory available.
Any request larger than this limit will not be processed.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="filenotfound"><cfoutput>File Not Found: #FORM.UpdateFilePath#</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_version">System Information</cfcase>
<cfcase value="version_pageHeader">
System Information</cfcase>
<cfcase value="need_upgrade"><cfoutput>You have entered an upgrade license key <b>(#FORM.new_license#)</b>,
which requires you to enter the license key of your previous version of ColdFusion.</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="cancel_upg">Cancel Upgrade</cfcase>
<cfcase value="old_license">Original license key</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ReportPack">Report Pack License</cfcase>
<cfcase value="update_file">Update File</cfcase>
<cfcase value="updatefilepath_instructions">Type in the directory that contains the update file. ColdFusion must have access to the file in order for it to be moved to the correct location within the runtime. You will need to restart ColdFusion Services for this change to take effect.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_versioninformation">System Information</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_serverdetails">Server Details</cfcase>
<cfcase value="serverprdvrsinf">Server Product</cfcase>
<cfcase value="vrsvrsinf">Version</cfcase>
<cfcase value="editionvrsinf">Edition</cfcase>
<cfcase value="sernlnumbervrsinf">Serial Number</cfcase>
<cfcase value="reportpacksernlnumbervrsinf">Report Pack Serial Number</cfcase>
<cfcase value="opsysiam">Operating System</cfcase>
<cfcase value="osversionxyz">OS Version</cfcase>
<cfcase value="updlevel">Update Level</cfcase>
<cfcase value="adobedriverversion">Adobe Driver Version</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_jvmdetails">JVM Details</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javaversionvrs">Java Version</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jvavendvrsninf">Java Vendor</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javavendurl">Java Vendor URL</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javahomeverioninfo">Java Home</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javafileencoding">Java File Encoding</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javalocale">Java Default Locale</cfcase>
<cfcase value="filesepjava">File Separator</cfcase>
<cfcase value="pathsepjvainfo">Path Separator</cfcase>
<cfcase value="linesepjavainfo">Line Separator</cfcase>
<cfcase value="usenamejavainfo">User Name</cfcase>
<cfcase value="userhomejavainfo">User Home</cfcase>
<cfcase value="userdirjavainfo">User Dir</cfcase>
<cfcase value="vmjavaspecversion">Java VM Specification Version</cfcase>
<cfcase value="sweetmaryjvmvendor">Java VM Specification Vendor</cfcase>
<cfcase value="specvmjavaname">Java VM Specification Name</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javavmversionyeah">Java VM Version</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jvavend">Java VM Vendor</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javavmname">Java VM Name</cfcase>
<cfcase value="versionjavaspec">Java Specification Version</cfcase>
<cfcase value="specfvendjaca">Java Specification Vendor</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javaspecnam">Java Specification Name</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jvaclsssvers">Java Class Version</cfcase>
<cfcase value="CFServerJavaClassPath">CF Server Java Class Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javaClassPath">Java Class Path</cfcase>
<cfcase value="javaextdirs">Java Ext Dirs</cfcase>
<cfcase value="l10n_printerdetails">Printer Details</cfcase>
<cfcase value="defaultprinter">Default Printer</cfcase>
<cfcase value="printers">Printers</cfcase>
<cfcase value="jvm_alert">For the hotfix to get applied, you must restart the ColdFusion Service.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="template_cache_size_error">The template cache size must be a number greater than or equal to zero.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="max_cached_queries_error">The maximum number of cached queries must be a number greater than or equal to zero.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="update_caching_error"><cfoutput>
Unable to update caching settings.<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#<br />
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="cache_too_big_error">Cache size must be an integer value greater than 0 and less than or equal to 1500.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="engines_too_big_error">The maximum number of threads must be an integer value greater than 0 and less than or equal to 5.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cache_path_error">You must specify a valid cache path. This must be an existing directory.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_error_tables">
Unable to create client tables <br />
If they already exist, you should uncheck Create Client Tables.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cv_error_timeout">
The timeout interval for purging client variables must be numeric.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="font_error_duplicate">
You cannot add duplicate fonts.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="font_error_empty_directory"><cfoutput>
Either directory "#CALLER.fontpath#" does not contain usable font files, or all the font files in the directory
have already been registered with the server.
Acceptable font extensions are: <br /><br />
                    TTF (True Type Font)<br />
                    TTC (True Type Collection)<br />
                    AFM (Adobe Font Metrics)<br />
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="font_error_add"><cfoutput>
Unable to add font '#CALLER.fontPath#'. Your path must be a valid absolute path. Acceptable paths are:<br /><br />
                        C:\myfonts\
                        C:\myfonts\tahoma.ttf<br />
                        C:\myfonts\gulim.ttc<br />
                        /opt/myfonts/<br />
                        /opt/myfonts/tahoma.ttf<br />
                        /opt/myfonts/gulim.ttc<br /><br />
                    Acceptable font extensions are: <br /><br />
                    TTF (True Type Font)<br />
                    TTC (True Type Collection)<br />
                    AFM (Adobe Font Metrics)<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="font_error_delete"><cfoutput>
Unable to delete your font.<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="set_jvm_error_update"><cfoutput>
Unable to update JVM settings.<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#<br />
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="get_jvm_error_update"><cfoutput>
Unable to retrieve JVM settings.<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#<br />
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="rl_error_limit"><cfoutput>
#CALLER.arguments.setting# limit must be numeric and greater than zero.
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="cfide_error_update">
Unable to update /CFIDE system mappings.<br />
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_error_update"><cfoutput>
Unable to update mappings.<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="map_error_get"><cfoutput>
Unable to retrieve mappings.<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#<br />
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="hours_error">Hours values must be numeric and between 0 and 23.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mins_error">Minutes values must be numeric and between 0 and 59.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="secs_error">Seconds values must be numeric and between 0 and 59.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="def_bigger_than_max_error">Default values cannot be larger than maximum values.</cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_error_update"><cfoutput>
Unable to update memory variables.<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#<br />
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="mem_error_get"><cfoutput>
Unable to retrieve memory variable settings.<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#<br />
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="local_config_error_add"><cfoutput>
Unable to configure local Office.
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="invalid_location_error"><cfoutput>
Specified directory #CALLER.dirpath# is not a valid Office installation
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="remote_config_error_add"><cfoutput>
Unable to configure remote OpenOffice.
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_error_timeout">
Timeout Requests length must be numeric and greater than one second.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_error_post_size">
Post Size must be numeric and greater than zero.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_error_throttle_threshold">
Throttle threshold must be numeric and greater than zero.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_error_throttle_memory">
Throttle memory must be numeric and greater than zero.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_error_inmemoryfilesystemlimit">
In-Memory File System limit must be numeric and greater than or equal to 1.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="cant_find_error_handler">
The file specified as the site wide error handler does not exist.
The default error handler will be used until a replacement is created.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_error_watch_interval">
Configuration watch interval must be numeric and greater than zero.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_error_cFaaSGeneratedFilesExpiryTime">
CFaaS created files deletion time must be numeric and greater than zero.
</cfcase>
<cfcase value="ss_error_tmpupd"><cfoutput>
Unable to update template handler information.
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Message#<br />
#CALLER.CFCATCH.Detail#<br />
</cfoutput></cfcase>
<cfcase value="errorheader">Error Handlers</cfcase>

<cfdefaultcase><cfset bSuccess="false"/></cfdefaultcase>
</cfswitch>
</cfprocessingdirective>

